RAVI RAJYAGURU

Full Stack Web Developer

ABOUT ME

With an experience of over 7+ years as a fullstack developer,

I have successfully delivered many projects in different service and product base sectors, With experience in domains like manufacturing, events, pharma, sports, e-

commerce, travel, booking, consultancy and many more.

I am having experience, starting from project understanding, planning, Design , deployment and Delivery. As a full-stack developer by nature, I always believe in logic not in syntax (being a RAM, not a hard disk). Because of experience in multiple frontends, backend languages. Hands on experience multiple servers technologies. I can choose which language, database and server will be best suitable for a product

along with the cost, time, and future expansion.

PASSION

Travel, Learn New Everyday, Work From Hills

SKILLS

Backend: Php, nodejs,python, Mysql, MongoDB

Frontend: Html, JQuery, Javascript, Vuejs, Angular, React, Redux, tailwindcss, Nextjs,

bootstrap

Framework: Laravel, Nextjs, ExpressJs, Django, Codeigniter

App development: Ionic, react native

CMS: Wordpress

Tools: Git, Jira, npm, AWS Services, Any Server Configurations, Third Party API integrations, Nginx, Apache, Socket.io, Amazon data synchronization, boto3 library Soft skills: Flexibility, Acceptance, Leader, Team Building, Ready to Accept new

challenge

CONTACT INFO:

+91 90337 94155

ravirajyaguru2@gmail.com LinkedIn: @dsravitech

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

B.E.IT

SILVER OAK COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING &TECHNOLOGY, GUJRAT: JUNE 2014

EXPERIENCE

DREAMSEEKER INFOTECH SEP 2019 TO PRESENT

Post: Freelance Full-Stack Web Developer Skills: Php, Laravel, Redis, Nodejs, Express, Vue, React, react native, Redux, AWS Elastic Beans, Dynamodb, MongoDB, AWS S3, Cloudflare, Cloudflare APIs, AWS EC2 Server Configuration And Deployment, Codepipeline Setup, Socket.Io, Django, Rest API, Javascript Obfuscate, Site Animations And Designs, Data Encryption, Handle High Traffic, Handle Site Security

VERTILEX WEB SOLUTION PVT. LTD APRIL 2016 TO AUGUST 2019

Post: Full Stack Developer And Project Manager Skills: Php, Wordpress, Woocommerce, Laravel, Angular, Ionic, AMazon Data Sync, Mysql, Server Configurations, Nodejs, DynamoDB, Mongodb Soft Skills: Project Requirement, Planing, Project design, Client Communications, Team Building, Agile Process

KGN TECHNOLOGIES SEP 2015 TO MARCH 2016

Post: WordPress Developer

Skills: Website development, Theme development,

Plugin Development

STEPIN SOLUTIONS JAN 2014 TO OCT 2015

Post: Junior Web developer

Skills: Php, Html, JQuery, Javascript, Mysql, 3rd Party APIs (FB login, Gmail Login, FB data Integrations), Rest

APIs

PROJECTS HIGHLIGHTS

KIDS CONNECTS

KidConect aims to help you make your kids become Superkids. We are parents who like all parents want our kids to understand all the basic values and principles of life. Technology driven learning which is equally fun and long lasting lesson.

My Role: Admin Panel, Parent app, child app Technology used: Laravel, react native, mysql, Vue

E-COMMERCE MARKETPLACE

This is a multi vendor ecommerce marketplace. Site have all marketplace functionality with payment integration and channel integration like amazon product sync and order sync.

My Role: WebSite Development, amazon channel integration

Technology used: PHP, Laravel,MySQL, Stripe Payment, Stripe Payout,HTML, jQuery.

MULTI SPORT CAMP SITE

This Is A Marketplace for Sports Academies, All Sport Academy Can Sell their Package Customize Site As Per Their Requirement.

My Role: Web development, Custom CMS development, Multi Site Session Management Technology used: PHP Core, MySQL, JQuery, Ajax.

EVENT MANAGEMENT APP

It is Event Listing Website And App Where All Running And Upcoming Events listed Around your 30km Area. My Role: Project Understanding, Project Management, Admin Side Development, Hybrid App Development, APIS Development

Technology used: Laravel, Mysql, Ionic, HTML, JQuery, Ajax

SALES APPLICATION

Application For Company Sales Department to Track location and sales And Take Orders From Vendors. This App has Check in, Checkout, Allowance Management, inventory management, orders.

My Role: Project Understanding, Project Management, Admin Side Development, Api Development, App Development

Technology used: Ionic, Laravel, Mysql, Jquery, Ajax, Location Tracking

FANTASY GAME DEVELOPMENT

This SIte Is Similar To Dream11

My Role: WebSite, Admin Panel, Score Master Panel

Development

Technology used: Nodejs, Express, React, Redux, Laravel, Vue, Aws Services, Socket.io, Payment Deposit

And Payment Withdrawal

SKILLED GAME DEVELOPMENT

This Game is For one to one User, in this User Select Their Player And Based On Player's Performance User Get Price.

My Role: Web Site, Admin Panel, Score Master Panel Development

Technology used: Nodejs, Express, React,Redux, Laravel, Vue, Aws Services, Socket.io, Payment Deposit And Payment Withdrawal

TRAVEL GUIDE APP

In This User Have Access to The place which Are Around the cite And Inside the city, in short its city quide app.

My Role: Admin Panel, APIs Development, Google Map API integrations

Technology used: Laravel, MySQL, HTML, JQuery, Ajax.

GRAB THE CHALLENGE

This App Is Social Network For A Person Who is Ready To Accept Challenge Like Racing, Running, Drag Racing.

My Role: Web Site, Admin Panel, Score Master Panel Development

Technology used: PHP, Mysql, AJax, JQuery, FB Login, FB APIs, Isotopes, APIs Development

ANDROID KIOSK APP

This Is Kiosk App For Company's Sales Team for tracking activity And Control Their Access.

My Role: Project Understanding, Project Management, Admin Side Development, APIs Development

Technology used: Angular, AWS S3, AWS Lambda, AWS DynamoDB, Nodejs